Guide to the Engineering Women's Club records, 1922-1992.
Engineering Women's Club records, 1922-1992.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Engineering Women's Club records, 1922-1992.
11-8-1563
Engineering Women's Club.
1.2 cubic ft.
Minutes, reports, correspondence, clippings, songs, constitution, and histories.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes of meetings, committee and membership lists, treasurer's reports, secretary's reports, annual reports, correspondence, clippings, songs, constitution, and histories of the Engineering Women's Club from its inception in 1922 until 1992.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Organization of faculty wives in the Cornell University College of Engineering.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes of meetings, committee and membership lists, treasurer's reports, secretary's reports, annual reports, correspondence, clippings, songs, constitution, and histories of the Engineering Women's Club from its inception in 1922 until 1992.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Engineering Women's Club.; Cornell University--Societies, etc.; Cornell University.College of Engineering.
Subjects:
Women--Societies and clubs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Minutes, 1922-1930 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Minutes, 1931-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 1936-1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Minutes, 1943-1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Minutes, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Minutes, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Minutes, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Minutes, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Minutes, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Records, 1922-1971 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
- Records, 1935-1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Records, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Records, 1971-1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Records, 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Records, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Volume IV, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Volume IV, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Volume IV, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- President's Book, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- President's Book, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- President's Book, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- President's Book, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- President's Book, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- President's Book, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- President's Book, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Secretary's Book, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Secretary's Book, 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Secretary's Book, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Secretary's Book, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Secretary's Book, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Secretary's Book, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Secretary's Book, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Treasurer's Report, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Treasurer's Report, 1939-1947 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Treasurer's Report, 1947-1958 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Treasurer's Report, 1958-1965 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Treasurer's Report, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Directories of all Engineering wives (members or no), 1960-1980 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Adopt-a-Family Project - French families letters, 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Adopt-a-Family Project - Greek family letters, 1946-1950 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
- Adopt-a-Family Project, 1946-1950 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 2 dessert-theater sign-up posters (Mapcase-folder 1)